Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
And what about that one?
That's Ursa Major.
Very good.
How about the big W there?
- Cassiopeia.
- Yeah.
And how about
that big, bright one?
- That's a planet.
- Very good.
Jupiter?
No, Jupiter we can't see
right now.
What's that smaller body
just off it?
- You see that?
- A moon.
Yeah.
- Is it Earth?
- Very good.
Dad!
Shh, shh.
Shh.
Remmy?
Remmy!
That's far enough.
He's coming, Remmy.
To here,
that one up here,
plus eight would be sixteen.
You would add one more.
That'd be 17.
So I put the one up here
and the one up here,
so that will be
eight plus nine.
- I don't know.
- Then let's go...
Dad!
Hey, hey, look at me.
Look at me.
We don't know
where we're from.
I'll get her to bed.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
What's up?
There are strangers nearby.
No.
No. It's just us.
I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared of.
You're fine on your own.
Are you gonna stay?
Are you?
If you leave the bed,
I'm gonna shave off
your eyebrows.
I will scream
the loudest possible scream
and follow you around
until they grow back.
I'll tie you up
with your own socks
and leave you
by the graves all night.
I will escape, steal the
lighter from where Mom hides it
and set the house on fire.
You mom and I are gonna
hold you by your ankles
and then slowly lower you
into the hole in the outhouse.
I will poop on your face
while you're sleeping.
Jesus.
See?
No one's gonna mess
with you, kid.
Good night.
You want me
to leave this one on?
- Yes, please.
- Okay.
Dad?
♪ And sweet and soft ♪
Okay, now you play.
Okay.
Um, I'll try.
I'll see if I remember.
♪ Your eyes take me back ♪
♪ To my childhood and my home ♪
♪ And though the light
May be dim ♪
Did you ever see a whale?
No.
How about you?
I wish.
An owl?
How about an elephant?
Nope.
Did you see anything?
Dogs.
Earth isn't what it once was,
you know.
Is that why you left?
We left because we wanted
something more.
We're very lucky
to have this place.
Why?
'Cause someday
it's gonna be just like Earth.
- We can talk about it more tomorrow.
- Okay.
You gonna stay?
Y... es.
Yes.
I love you very much.
Love you.
Good night.
'Night.
Reza!
Don't move, okay?
You stay right here.
- I told you!
- Shut up!
What's going on?
Fuck.
Do you see anything?
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
What if it's his son?
Don't.
I count six.
No.
They're changing their voices.
There are only three.
Come on.
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
I think the other pig
is still alive.
Hello?
Let it go, Rem.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Me, too.
First rule?
Stay calm.
Stay alive.
Hey.
You are in very, very
good hands, okay.
Remmy!
Get in here!
Get in here right now!
Get inside!
- Do you have Remmy?
- Yes!
I need your eyes on the ridge!
You see anything?
I see him!
- Is he still at the sun?
- Yes!
You lock the door behind me.
- It's gonna be dark soon.
- I know.
Dad, Dad!
You stay with your mother.
Dad!
Get inside,
get inside now!
Hey.
Okay?
Turn it off.
Mom.
I have to go to the bathroom.
We'll use this.
Come on.
It's okay.
What's going on?
The main lights went off.
Stay here.
Mom.
Drop the blade.
Drop it.
This place doesn't
belong to you.
It was my parents'.
And I don't know
what you did to them.
I don't really care,
but I was born here,
I was raised here,
and I've come a long,
long way to get back.
And I'm here to stay.
I don't wanna hurt you.
So you can leave if you want.
But I'm pretty
sure that you know
what's waiting
for you out there.
I know how to get this
place back on its feet.
And I can protect you.
If you behave.
Stay in sight.
We can go, Mommy, we can go.
Mom, we can go, please?
- I know, I know, listen.
- Please let us go, Mommy.
Listen, I'm not gonna
let anything happen to you.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Okay?
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Hey.
I will be right back, okay?
I want you to stay right here.
Promise?
Yeah, okay.
If you move another muscle,
your kid is gonna
be alone with me.
Think!
How is killing me
going to help you?
Okay.
Here's the deal.
For 30 days you don't pull
another stunt like this on me,
I will take this gun,
put it on that table over there,
turn my back around and
walk out on to that porch.
30 days.
And you'll get your chance,
if you still want it.
I want my husband buried.
Stay as long as you need.
We can leave.
Mom, we can leave now.
No, Rem, we can't.
We need to talk.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
Luckily we have
everything that we need
to get this place
back on its feet.
Fuck off.
Okay.
Taps should be running,
by the way.
Remmy!
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, it's harmless.
Don't touch me.
What's his name?
It's just a tool.
This is very good.
Can I go play with Steve?
Steve?
The robot, I named him Steve.
Sure.
Can I take your plate?
And... catch.
Yay.
Come here.
Catch.
My name's Jerry, by the way.
My parents ever mention me?
Guess not.
Guess there was no point.
Made it pretty clear
I was never coming back.
Leave me alone.
I didn't wanna be here either,
you know.
There was nowhere else left.
Cities, other settlements,
all gone.
She's a cute kid.
I didn't kill your mother.
That's good of you.
She was already
dead when we got here.
I never saw any of your cities.
Our transport got shot down
when we entered the atmosphere.
Your dad took us in.
Then one day, when I was
seven months pregnant,
he stuck a rifle in our faces
and told us to leave.
Why would he do
a thing like that?
He figured it out,
that we were from Earth.
So I slit his throat with
the knife you just washed.
If you touch her,
I'll carve your heart out.
You could empty out a whole gun
of yours into me,
I'd still get to you.
You assume a lot about me.
I see no reason why
I'd need to touch her.
Can Steve
sleep with us?
I don't think it sleeps.
Come on.
Good night.
Get into bed,
I'll be right there.
Hi, hey, Cassy.
Wait here, Steve.
Come on, Cassy.
Yes.
You in there, kid?
Hey, so I know,
I know that I'm not supposed to
be talking to you,
but I lost something
from a notebook I keep.
An old drawing.
You wouldn't know
anything about that?
Do you think maybe
Steve took it?
Anyways, um, I just came
to tell him
that he can keep it.
I won't snitch.
All right?
Remmy?
Smells good.
Where's the kid?
Just called her.
Are you getting up?
Have you seen Remmy?
Go away, Steve, it's not safe.
Go!
Go.
And tell my mom that she
can have another daughter.
With Jerry!
Remmy!
Hard to miss, isn't it?
Once you know it's there.
I was eight when
my parents told me.
So you wanna know
what's out there?
Obviously.
Nothing.
Sand, a rock.
There was once more,
but it's all gone now,
or will be soon.
Then where did you come from?
From the war, for less and less.
I don't believe you.
Ever notice that the
sunrises are getting bluer?
What is that?
It's from the dust
in the atmosphere.
An atmosphere that we
created and maintained.
It's all just blowing
off into space.
I know it's a hard thing
to hear,
you know, but the sooner
that you accept it,
the sooner you'll realize
how lucky we are
to have this place.
We...
we have everything
we need,
right here.
Rem, stop playing
with your food.
Come on, you gotta eat.
You don't like sweet potatoes?
I used to not like them either.
I'm going back to my bed, Rem.
I think I know what
you're feeling right now.
I would feel the same way.
I just need you to know
that I loved your father
and I love you more
than you will ever know.
Forgot about this.
Wanna learn how to play?
You?
- Little bit.
- Really?
How about a song?
Been a long time since
I heard any music.
Sure.
Come.
Sorry.
♪ Your eyes take me back ♪
♪ To my childhood ♪
♪ And my home ♪
♪ And though the light
May be dim ♪
♪ The taste of your lips
Is sweet ♪
♪ Like the first wine
Of the... ♪
Remmy.
Remmy, please.
I need you to trust me.
Remmy.
I hate you.
Everything okay?
Mm-hmm.
You okay?
Yeah.
She's, uh...
She's just adjusting.
Hmm.
You don't have to.
Nah, I'm just tired
of it weighing me down.
So.
Think about your daughter.
I am.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Please, please, please.
No, no, no, no!
Listen, everything's
gonna be okay.
I'm never gonna hurt you.
I just need you to stay.
I just need you to stay
until I say you can.
Okay?
Can you do that?
You can come inside now.
Remmy.
It's okay.
When you're ready.
Seven piggies in a row,
if he hollers, then you'll know
he's the pig who wants to go.
My mother said
to pick the second best one
and it's Y-O-U.
I was thinking.
You might want to give it a go.
I'm going to the valley
tomorrow morning.
Isn't that exciting?
I'll need Steve...
if that's okay with you.
He's agreed, provided
that we are back by lunch.
I pointed out that
he doesn't eat lunch.
And he looks back at me with
that steely gaze of his,
and he says,
"Jerry,
we've talked about this."
I saw that.
Eleventh time this year.
Wild times.
Who goes there?
Remmy?
Is that you?
I knew it.
You missed me?
You should hop in.
It's murky but it's clean.
And it feels so good.
I'll leave a blanket for you.
Enjoy.
Want a drink?
Go on.
Careful now with that one,
the batch is strong.
What do you think?
Cheers.
Hey, I, I have
something for you.
I think you're gonna like it.
Sit over here.
Go on, just, just take it.
It helps that you grew up
to look so much like her.
She'd be so proud of you, Remmy.
It's okay.
It's okay, come on.
Okay.
Come on.
It's okay.
So how was your day?
You know there's no rush.
The important thing is
that you feel comfortable.
You know?
All those things that you're
feeling are completely normal.
I can't do it.
Hey.
You can't do what?
It's okay.
Like I said,
we've got plenty of time.
Ever.
You're still young.
You're not listening to me.
I haven't had
much practice lately.
We've been through this before.
This is bigger than you and me.
I'm not about to give up.
That's very noble of you.
A man's gotta stand
for something.
If you try to force one
inside of me, I will kill it.
Do you know how to do that?
'Cause I do.
Pretty dangerous if you don't.
And then where would
you be without me?
I don't know.
About where I am now, I guess.
Gotten pretty good
talking to myself.
So what are you waiting for?
Is that what you want?
Hmm?
If I just held you down
and did it?
So you can just keep on
pretending like I'm the bad guy?
Go on hating me?
I don't hate you, Jerry.
Then what is it?
You think it over some more.
I have.
Leave me alone, Steve.
You going somewhere?
Give it back!
If you leave, you're gonna
die in a day, maybe two.
Stop pretending like
you're doing this for me.
Okay, all of this,
all of this I did for you!
If you think there's someone
out there, you're wrong.
I'm it, okay?
Me!
Give me back my mask.
- You can't control me!
- You're my responsibility.
- Yeah, and why's that?
- Well, because someone couldn't
accept the reality
of her situation!
Well, this time you
don't have a child
to use to pressure
me into your bed.
Okay, you want
your fucking mask?
Huh?
You want your mask?
Here's your fucking mask!
Okay, this is how
it will feel, okay.
This is how it'll end!
Hmm!
It's okay. Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's just,
it's okay, it's...
It's just so that we can talk.
It's okay.
- No!
- It's just so that we can talk.
- Jerry.
- Hey, it's okay.
Please.
- I'm sorry.
- Jerry.
Okay, I'm sorry. It's...
But, but you leave
and then you're dead.
And then that will be it.
- Okay.
Okay.
And, and I just, I just,
I just can't risk that,
not, not while there's
still some sort of hope.
Okay?
Jerry.
- Jerry, please.
- Hey, hey, hey, wait.
Listen to me.
Can you listen to me?
We both have
a responsibility, okay?
You and me.
Which neither of us asked for.
Okay?
You all keep making me
do these terrible things.
- Yes, we need to...
- No.
- I need you to understand how important this is.
Please, I need you
to understand
- that this is so important.
- Okay.
- Okay, it's okay, it's okay.
- Let me go.
- No, it's okay.
Let me go!
- Okay, it's okay.
- Let me go!
It's okay, it's okay,
you're okay.
It's just... shh, shh.
It doesn't have to be bad.
It doesn't have to be like...
please, not like this.
- It's okay.
- Please, not like this.
- Let me go, Jerry.
Let me go, Jerry,
Jerry, let me go!
- Stop it.
- Let me leave!
Stop it!
Just stop it!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Okay.
Stop it.
Hmm, okay stop it.
It doesn't have to be bad.
Just, just...
Okay, just.
Okay, just close your eyes.
God!
You need me as much
as I need you.
I disagree.
Hello!
I'm going, Steve.
You have to stay here.
Don't look at me like that.
This is your place now, okay?
Do you hate me?
Yeah, me neither.
The opposite.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull